MARSHALL BRUNER

Denver, CO

८ +1 970-568-6162 **☑** brunerm99@gmail.com **⋒** marshall-bruner **⊘** brunerm99

OBJECTIVE

I am pursuing a transition to a software-centered role. My experience in this area ranges from writing firmware for electronics used in flight to configuring webservers for radar data visualization and analysis. I would like to use this experience as a baseline for contributing to a team and developing my skills further.

EXPERIENCE

Jun. 2021 — Present **Ball Aerospace** Broomfield, CO

RF Engineer

• Used Python knowledge to create useful plotting and RF analysis tools

- Simulated, designed, and tested an RF Front-End PWB at extreme temperatures
- Debugged complex, mission-critical RF boards under strict time constraints
- Built an embedded webpage used to interact with a phased array antenna
- High sensitivity testing (noise, high power, etc.) of electonics

Colorado State University

Graduate Research Assistant — Thesis

Jan. 2021 — May 2022 Fort Collins, CO

- Design, schematic, and layout of a modular, X-band, FMCW drone radar
- Signal processing / data visualization for Analog Device's FMCW Phaser Board
- Presented the work at the IEEE Internation Phased Array Symposium
- Phaser board work was presented by ADI at IMS 2022 and IEEE-APS 2022
- Built a server to host and display real-time and historical radar data using Post-GreSQL, Flask, Python

CHILL Radar Lab May 2020 — May 2021 Lab Assistant Greeley, CO

• Built a real-time radar display to easily display and animate radar data

• Performed characterizations and measurements of radar equipment

EDUCATION

Colorado State University

Jan. 2021 — May 2022

M.S. Electrical Engineering — GPA: 3.9

Fort Collins, CO

Thesis - Design, Deployment, and Cost Considerations for DARMA; A Low-Cost and Lightweight FMCW Radar

Colorado State University

Aug. 2017 — May 2021

B.S. Electrical Engineering — GPA: 3.47

Fort Collins, CO

PROJECTS

5G Electronics Senior Design Project

Jun. 2020 — May 2021

- Simulated, assembled, and measured a full 5G receiver system
- Created teaching documentation for a 5G transmitter and receiver for FR1 and FR2 frequency bands
- Experience using FieldFox, EMPro, ADS, SystemVue

Fuzzy Logic Clutter Filter

Nov. 2020 - Dec. 2020

• Applied the Fuzzy Logic machine learning technique to radar data to filter clutter

Environment-Mapping Car

Nov. 2020 - Dec. 2020

 Built and programmed a battery-powered car with attached ultrasonic sensor for mobile mapping of the surrounding environment

SKILLS & ABILITIES

Languages: Python, SQL, C, Bash, Matlab, JavaScript, HTML, CSS

Technologies / Tools: Git, IATEX, Linux, Docker, PostGreSQL/TimescaleDB, Flask, Celery (Distributed Tasks)

Communication: Excellent Technical Communication and Presentation Skills, Experience Presenting PDR/CDRs,

Technical Paper/Presentation Formatting, Concise Code Documentation